suas.ac.in 2019-03-05

# Privacy Policy» Symbiosis University of Applied Sciences (SUAS)

**Symbiosis University of Applied Sciences (SUAS)** **Privacy Policy**

This Privacy policy sets out how Symbiosis University of Applied Sciences (SUAS) uses, maintains and protects any information gathered from “Users” visiting the website www.suas.ac.in

Symbiosis University of Applied Sciences (SUAS) may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You need to check this page from time to time to ensure that you are aware of the changes.

**Personal** **identification information:**

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, place an order, respond to a query or survey, fill out an online form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, details such as name, email address,

Phone number, contact information and date of birth etc. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may limit them from engaging in certain Site related activities

**Non-personal** **identification information:**

We may also collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. The non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer used and technical information about Users means of connection to our Sites, such as the operating system used and the details of the Internet service provider utilized and other similar information.

**Web** **browser cookies:**

Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance the overall User experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drives for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. Users may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies or to alert you when cookies are being sent. However, if they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

**Usage and Protection of collected information:**

We use the personal identification information primarily to enhance and personalize the overall user experience, improve the site, to run promotions, surveys and to send periodic emails if required.

We do not share or sell the data to third parties and adopt industry-standard data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site. All the sensitive and private data exchange between the Site and its Users happens over an SSL secured communication channel.

**Your** **acceptance of these terms:**

By using this Site, you confirm your acceptance of this policy. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes therein.
